wisesample.com 2017-10-20

# Privacy Policy || WiseSample

## WiseSample.com is strongly committed to safeguarding your privacy with us

WiseWorks (together with its affiliates, the "Company") owns and operates a number of different websites, mobile apps, and interactive services, including without limitation WiseSample.com, Flapbucks.com, WisePerks.com, and others (collectively, the "WiseWorks Sites"). This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") applies to the WiseWorks Sites and to all of the features, mobile applications, emails, online services and other functionalities, whether accessed via a computer, mobile device, or otherwise and the services available on or through the WiseWorks Sites and Features (the "Services"). This Privacy Policy only covers information collected by the Company through the WiseWorks Sites and Features and our Services, and does not cover any information received or collected offline by the Company (unless specifically stated) or collected by any unrelated websites or companies to which we may provide links. 

The following privacy policy explains how your personal information is held and treated as you explore our website and services.

What personally identifiable information does WiseSample.com collect from me?

WiseSample.com collects information in several manners from different parts of our website and network. Some information is gathered when you sign up. During member registration, WiseSample.com asks for your name, email address, zip code and household information. The more information you volunteer to provide accurately, the better we are able to offer you services and rewards. Additionally, if you ever contact WiseSample.com through any means, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Whenever WiseSample.com collects any such information, we aim to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

What are cookies and how does WiseSample.com use them?

A cookie is a packet of electronic data sent to your browser, from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. As part of offering you specific surveys, information, and personalized services, WiseSample.com may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. WiseSample.com may require that you accept cookies for preparing such specific content for you. This also avoids you having to enter your login information every time.

Who is collecting information and for what purpose?

WiseSample.com collects several information through surveys and registration and other means, which helps its research clients develop new products and services for consumers. You are sharing that information with WiseSample.com only, unless it is specifically stated otherwise on any survey you participate. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than WiseWorks -- or WiseWorks sites, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. If you do not want your data to be shared, you may choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular survey or product.

Rewards and promotions that we offer on WiseSample.com may be either sponsored by other companies independently, or may be co-sponsored by WiseSample.com and another company. Some data collected during such a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. However, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer. You can decide not to participate in that particular promotion if you do not want to share your data.

Any specific Sensitive Information (like information specifying medical or health conditions, racial or ethnic origin, political views, religious or spiritual beliefs, trades and union membership or information specifying the sex life of the individual) will be treated with additional care. If WiseSample.com intends to share such information to another company for a different purpose than originally collected, then you will be expressly asked permission prior to any such disclosure.

With whom does WiseSample.com share my information?

We take privacy very seriously. WiseSample.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your explicit permission or under any special circumstances, that the law requires it or under the circumstances specified in detail below.

The following describes some of the ways that your information may be disclosed. Please see the Terms of Service for our services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared.

## Business Partners, Clients & Sponsors:

WiseSample.com may disclose your personal information to our partners, clients or sponsors. However, if any personal data about you were ever to be shared, we will tell you before we collect or transfer the data. Many activities we offer request additional information from sponsors. By you requesting more information, you give WiseSample.com permission to share your information with the sponsor so they can fulfill your request. In many instances, only your email address will be shared. If more information will be shared with our partners, you will be notified in advance. From time to time, you may be offered the opportunity to receive test materials, or other products or special offers from our partners. If you opt-in to receive information from these third parties, WiseSample.com will (with your permission) share your name and email address with them.

WiseSample.com may also disclose personal information in some special cases when disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating WiseSample.com 's policies and Terms of Service or may be causing any injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) WiseSample.com 's products, services, rights or property, other WiseSample.com members and users, or anyone else that could be affected by any such activities. WiseSample.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.

What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?

Only WiseSample.com (or partners working with WiseSample.com under confidentiality agreements) will send you any direct mails, only if you indicated that you do not object to these. You also have choices with respect to how cookies work. By changing your internet browser settings, you have the choice to accept all cookies, notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies request. If you choose to reject all cookies, you will be unable to use those WiseSample.com services that do require prior registration in order to participate. WiseSample.com does not sell or lease any user information to anyone. We will always notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with any third party and you will always have the option of not allowing it to be shared. 

What is WiseSample.com’s policy on allowing me to update, edit, change or delete my personal account information?

You may edit your WiseSample.com Account Information any time by using your WiseSample.com Log in and password. Please contact [Feedback@WiseSample.com](mailto:feedback@wisesample.com) for further instructions about deactivating your WiseSample.com account.

What security precautions are in place at WiseSample.com to protect any loss, misuse, or alteration of my account information?

Your WiseSample.com Account Information are password-protected so that you and only you have access to this information. We strongly recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email. Please sign out of your WiseSample.com account and close your browser window when you have finished your activity. This ensures that others cannot access your personal information and account, if you are using a public computer or share your computer with someone else. Whenever WiseSample.com handles personal information as described above, regardless of where this occurs, WiseSample.com takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, WiseSample.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your data, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

What else should I know about my privacy?

Please keep in mind that whenever (and wherever) you choose to disclose personal information online - for example through emails, social networking websites, blogs, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by any other user. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

How does WiseSample.com protect the privacy of my children? 

WiseSample.com obtains prior parental consent where surveys require children to participate and parental supervision is also required for any such surveys with children ages 6-15. We take special extra care to protect the safety and privacy of young users on our site, and we encourage you to participate in your child's experience online. We do not permit any marketing or in children's research and the certain topics are completely prohibited in research among children: Name/account name/E-mail or physical address, Phone number, Race or Ethnicity, Religion or Cast, Household income, Family illness, Marital status of parents or other family members, Relationship matters, Grades in school or college, Alcohol, Sexual Issues, Tobacco and Firearms.

## Additional Information

Any other questions regarding this should be sent to [letstalk@wisesample.com!](mailto:letstalk@wisesample.com!)
